

GRAPHIC/UX DESIGNER



agrayson91@gmail.com



anthonygrayson.com



206-899-7703

I have done freelance design work for several years. In additon, I have my bachelors in graphic/web design from Southern New Hampshire University. My design style is user-focused simplicity. In my philosophy, simple and effective design can be used in a multitude of ways while effectively telling a story about who the person is or what the business stands for. Every project I've taken on is done with attention to detail and love for design.

EDUCATION

Southern New Hampshire University

BA Graphic Design and Media Arts w/conc in Web Design, 2018-2021

- Deans list, Winter 2019
- Learned and mastered principles of Graphic, Web and UX design

EXPERIENCE

Quiring Monuments

2020 - Present

Graphic Designer

Successfully executed hundreds of design requests for monuments from customers. Illustrated custom graphics and typefaces to the customer's satisfaction with empathy and careful precision.

Ceres Garden

2019 - 2020

Graphic Designer/Retail Support

Lead in the design, development, and implementation of the graphic, layout, and production communication materials. Supervised the assessment of all graphic materials in order to ensure quality and accuracy of the design.

Fastsigns

2017 - 2018

Graphic Designer

Received inquiries and implemented design requests from clients. Successfully executed the design and production of signs requested by clients.

Freelance

2011 - Present

Graphic Designer

Successfully implemented and executed design inquiries from clients. My work includes business and personal logos, business cards, fliers, posters, apparel design and book covers.

SKILLS

· Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator,

XD, Dreamweaver)

- Web Development (HTML, CSS, Javascript)
- Illustration
- · Skilled in both Mac and PC platforms.